zippycourses.com 2019-06-14

# 

Thank you for visiting [www.zippycourse.com](http://www.zippycourses.com/) and its affiliated sites and reviewing our Privacy Policy. This website is owned and operated by DHJW Software LLC dba “Zippy Courses™”. This Privacy Policy explains what type of information we collect from our visitors on this website and in the course of our relationship, what we do with that information, and how users can update and control the use of information provided on the website. This Privacy Policy does not describe information collection practices on other websites, including those linked to or from our website. As further set out below, this Privacy Policy may change from time to time so please check it frequently.

The Internet is an amazing tool. It has the power to change the way we live, and we’re starting to see that potential today. With only a few mouse-clicks, you can follow the news, look up facts, buy goods and services, and communicate with others from around the world. It’s important to DHJW Software LLC dba “Zippy Courses™”, the owner and operator of[www.zippycourses.com](http://www.zippycourses.com/) to help our users retain their privacy when they take advantage of all the Internet has to offer.

We believe your business is no one else’s. Your privacy is important to you and to us. So we’ll protect the information you share with us. To protect your privacy, DHJW Software LLC dba “Zippy Courses™” follows different principles in accordance with worldwide practices for customer privacy and data protection.

  * We won’t sell or give away your name, mail address, phone number, email address or any other information to anyone except as permitted by this Privacy Policy.
  * We’ll use security measures to protect your information from unauthorized users.

## NOTICE

When you purchase and install the Software, we ask you to register and create an account. When you do, we create a personal profile for you from your registration information. We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”) or enables us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you create an account subscription on the website, download our Software, or signup for email newsletters. We use your Personal Information for four primary purposes:

  * To make the website easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.
  * To help you quickly find Software or information.
  * To help us create content most relevant to you.
  * To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information, and other new services from us.

## CONSENT

If you choose not to register or provide Personal Information, you can still review the website but you will not be able to access areas that require registration.

If you decide to register, you will be able to select the kinds of information you want to receive from us by subscribing to various services, like our electronic newsletters. If you do not want us to communicate with you about other offers regarding DHJW Software LLC dba “Zippy Courses™” products, programs, events, or services by email, postal mail, or telephone, you may select the option stating that you do not wish to receive marketing messages from us.

## ACCESS

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your Personal Information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time in your account. There, you can:

  * View and edit Personal Information you have already given us.
  * Tell us whether you want us to send you marketing information.
  * Sign up for electronic newsletters about our services and products.
  * Register. Once you register, you won’t need to do it again. Wherever you go on[www.zippycourses.com](http://www.zippycourses.com/), your information stays with you.

## OPTING OUT

You may tell us not to share your information with our affiliates (meaning companies under common control or ownership) for their own marketing purposes or with unaffiliated business partners as part of a joint marketing arrangement. Even if you don’t “opt out,” we will not share your information with unaffiliated companies for their own marketing purposes except as part of a joint marketing arrangement. You can also “opt out” anytime by contacting us at: [support@zippycourses.com](mailto:support@zippycourses.com).

## WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION YOU SHARE

When you join us, you provide us with your contact information, including your name and email address. We use this information to send you updates about your order and advertising and announcements about new and exciting services that we offer. We may also use your email address internally for retargeting purposes and to create custom audiences on social media websites like Facebook.

When you order from us, through our third-party shopping cart and payment processing providers, we ask for your credit card number and billing address. This information is stored with the third-party shopping cart and payment processing providers so they can authorize your payment. We use this information only to bill you for the Software you order at that time and for any subscription or renewals you have ordered. We use the third-party providers to help reduce the risk of your payment information being inadvertently released or deliberately accessed by an unauthorized person.

Your Personal Information is never shared outside the company without your permission except as described in this Privacy Policy and subject to your rights in this Privacy Policy to grant or withhold permission. DHJW Software LLC dba “Zippy Courses™” is permitted to disclose your Personal Information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with applicable legal requirements or comply with legal process served on DHJW Software LLC dba “Zippy Courses™” or the website; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of DHJW Software LLC dba “Zippy Courses™” and its website, [www.zippycourses.com](http://www.zippycourses.com/), and, (c) act in good faith in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of other users of DHJW Software LLC dba “Zippy Courses™”, its websites, or the public.

## CORPORATE TRANSACTIONS

If the company or the website is sold, we may transfer your Personal Information to the extent reasonable to allow the buyer to continue to provide the relevant services to you. If the company is sold in its entirety, your Personal Information will remain the property of the company. If the website is sold, your Personal Information will be transferred with your account as appropriate so that you may continue to receive the services to which you are entitled and to receive the benefits that we have offered to you. DHJW Software LLC dba “Zippy Courses™” will make these determinations about the transfer of your Personal Information in good faith. If we were unable to transfer your Personal Information under these circumstances, we could be unable to sell the company or the website and you could lose access to the services to which you would be entitled.

## SECURITY

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. DHJW Software LLC dba “Zippy Courses™” is committed to ensuring that your information is secure, and we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet is 100% secure, however we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

When you order the Software and/or access your Personal Information, you are using SSL secure server technology, which encrypts your Personal Information before it is transmitted over the Internet.

We engage third-party shopping carts, payment processing providers, or service providers to help us process customer credit cards, which information is governed by our third-party service providers’ privacy policies. For more information on the privacy policies for our service providers who are collecting Personal Information for credit card processing, please see their individual privacy policies.

You also have a significant role in protecting your Personal Information. No one can see or edit your Personal Information without knowing your user name and password, so do not share these with others.

If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at: support@zippycourses.com.

## COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer hard drive. Cookies help analyze web traffic and allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie does not give us access to your computer or any information about you other than the data you choose to make available.

We use cookies on this website and log files to: (a) provide custom, personalized content and information; (b) monitor the effectiveness of our Software; and (c) monitor metrics such as user activity, total number of visitors, and pages viewed along with downloads and duration of views.

In order to ensure that our software is working efficiently and effectively for each student, we also use our Zippy Courses™ tracking technology to track the following data, (a) The number of websites that install Zippy Courses™, (b) the number of students in our courses; (c) the license key for each website that downloads our software.

## LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

If you click on a link to a third party website, you will leave our website and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personally identifiable information by such third parties, and those sites are of course not governed by this Privacy Policy. We strongly encourage you to review the privacy statements of any other service provider from whom you request services.

## NOTICE TO PARENTS

Parents or guardians: we want to help you guard your children’s privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet. This website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13.

## ENFORCEMENT

If for some reason you believe we have not adhered to these principles, please notify us by email at [support@zippycourses.com](mailto:support@zippycourses.com), and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the subject line.

## DATA PROTECTION

All definitions used in this clause shall have the definition set out in the Data Protection Legislation.

The Controller (you) and the Processor (Zippy Courses) acknowledge that the Controller is the controller and the Processor is the processor and that the Controller retains control of the Personal Data and remains responsible for its compliance obligations under Data Protection Legislation. The Processor may process the Personal Data categories and Data Subject types set out in the [Zippy Courses Platform Data Processing Agreement](https://zippy.helpscoutdocs.com/article/226-zippy-courses-all-in-one-platform-data-processing-agreement). Each party agrees to comply with all applicable requirements of the Data Protection Legislation. 

The Processor shall:

  * implement appropriate technical and organisational measures in such a manner that processing will meet the requirements of Data Protection Legislation and ensure the protection of the rights of the Data Subject; 
  * only authorise a third party (“sub-processor”) to process the Personal Data if (i) the Processor has obtained the prior written consent from the Controller for each appointment of a sub-processor and (ii) the Processor and the sub-processor enter into a written contract containing terms the same as those set out in this clause, in particular, in relation to data security measures and (iii) the Processor maintains control over all Personal Data it shares with the sub-processor and (iv) the Processor ensures that the sub-processor does not process the Personal Data except on instructions from the Data Controller (unless required to do so by Union or Member State law); 
  * process the Personal Data only on documented instructions from the Controller, unless required to do so by Data Protection Legislation to which the Processor is subject; in such a case, the Processor shall inform the Controller of that legal requirement before processing, unless that law prohibits such information on important grounds of public interest; ensure that persons authorised to process the personal data (such as its employees) have committed themselves to confidentiality or are under an appropriate statutory obligation of confidentiality; 
  * ensure that is has in place appropriate technical and organisational measures, reviewed and approved by the Controller, to ensure a level of security appropriate to the risk (taking into account the state of the art, the costs of implementation and the nature, scope, context and purposes of processing as well as the risk of varying likelihood and severity for the rights and freedoms of Natural Persons) including, where appropriate, the pseudonymisation and encryption of Personal Data, the ability to ensure the ongoing confidentiality, integrity, availability and resilience of processing systems and services, the ability to restore the availability and access to Personal Data in a timely manner in the event of a physical or technical incident and a process for regularly testing, assessing and evaluating the effectiveness of the technical and organisational measures for ensuring the security of processing. Account shall also be taken of the risks that are presented by the processing in particular from accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorised disclosure of, or access to personal data transmitted, stored or otherwise processed; 
  * taking into account the nature of the processing, assist the Controller by appropriate technical and organisational measures, insofar as this is possible, for the fulfilment of the Controller’s obligation to respond to requests for exercising the Data Subject’s rights set out in Chapter III of the GDPR; 
  * assist the Controller in ensuring compliance with the obligations set out in Articles 32 to 36 of the GDPR (data breach) taking into account the nature of processing and the information available to the Processor; 
  * at the choice of the Controller, delete or return all the Personal Data to the Controller after the termination or expiry of this Agreement and delete existing copies (unless Union or Member State law requires storage of the Personal Data); 
  * make available to the Controller all information necessary to demonstrate compliance with the obligations laid down in Article 28 of the GDPR and allow for and contribute to audits, including inspections, conducted by the Controller or another auditor mandated by the Controller; 
  * assist the Controller in ensuring compliance with the requirement to carry out Data Protection Impact Assessments as set out in Article 35 of GDPR, taking into account the nature of processing and the information available to the Processor; 
  * immediately inform the Controller, if in the opinion of the Processor, an instruction from the Controller infringes Data Protection Legislation; 
  * promptly comply with any request by or instruction from the Controller to process the Personal Data, or to stop, mitigate or remedy any unauthorised processing; 
  * keep all Personal Data confidential and not disclose such data to third parties unless specifically authorised in writing by the Controller or as required by law. If the Processor is required by law, court, regulator or supervisory authority to process or disclose any Personal Data, the Processor will first inform the Controller of this and allow the Controller to object or challenge the requirement, unless the law prohibits the Processor from informing the Controller; 
  * not transfer or otherwise process Personal Data outside the European Economic Area (EEA) without obtaining the Controller’s prior written consent (except where the Processor is required to transfer such data by Union or Member State law, in which case the Processor shall inform the Controller of such legal requirement before processing takes place, unless any law prohibits such disclosure on important grounds of public interest) and (i) there is an appropriate safeguard or derogation for such transfer in accordance with part V of the GDPR; 
  * keep detailed, accurate and up-to-date written records regarding any processing of Personal Data it carries out for the Controller, using the schedule set out in schedule 3 or in such form as the Controller may require from time to time (Records) and shall make them available to the the Controller upon request. 

## NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES; EFFECTIVE DATE

DHJW Software LLC dba “Zippy Courses™” reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to change, modify or otherwise alter the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such changes and/or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting and your continued use of the website following the posting of such changes/modification will constitute your acceptance of the revised terms of the Privacy Policy. It is and will be your responsibility to review our Privacy Policy from time to time to make sure you are aware of any changes. This Privacy Policy is effective with respect to all data that we have collected since the date we started collecting data, which was July 25 2014.

## QUESTIONS

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or our collection of your information, feel free to contact us by sending an email to support@zippycourses.com or by U.S. mail to DHJW Software LLC dba “Zippy Courses™”, 734 Franklin Avenue, Suite #292, Garden City, New York 11530.

## DEFINITIONS

**Data Protection Legislation:** all applicable data protection laws including General Data Protection Regulation ((EU) 2016/679) (“GDPR”) and any applicable national data protection legislation, regulations and secondary legislation from time to time in force in the jurisdiction of the Controller and/or the Processor relating to the processing of Personal Data, and where relevant the Privacy and Electronic Communications Directive (2002/58/EC) and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 (SI 2003/2426).
